(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-07T18:08:08.435637",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
FuRyu
フリュー
Breaking Dimensions hololive English 2nd Concert
[hololive English 2nd Concert: Breaking Dimensions]
BREAKING NEWS !! from FuRyu
[Breaking News from FuRyu]
Starting around JANUARY 2025 at ROUND1 across the US!
[Starting around January 2025 at Round 1 across the US!]
PUPPET PLUSHIES
LYING DOWN PLUSHIES
hololive plushies up for grabs in ROUND1 CRANE GAMES!
[Hololive plushies up for grabs in Round 1 Crane Games!]
FuRyu
BREAKING NEWS !! from FuRyu
[Breaking News from FuRyu]
Starting around JANUARY 2025 at ROUND1 across the US!
[Starting around January 2025 at Round 1 across the US!]
hololive plushies up for grabs in ROUND1 CRANE GAMES!
[Hololive plushies up for grabs in Round 1 Crane Games!]
ROUND1
[Round 1]
Further updates will be posted on ROUND1 website, be sure to check regularly!
[Further updates will be posted on Round 1 website, be sure to check regularly!]
hololive campaign at ROUND1 starting October 2024!
[Hololive campaign at Round 1 starting October 2024!]
NOW AVAILABLE GLOBALLY FOR PRE-ORDER ON HYTE.COM
ohmonah BREAKING DIMENSIONS
holoplus - hololive production's Official App
FuRyu
ENigmatic Recollection
フリュー
FuRyu
Roses are red, the fire of my heart is blue. Also known as the Scarlet Queen, the harbinger of order, leader of justice! I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame.
Lovely to see it, to see ya. Lovely!
It's Gigi Murin! But today, what are they going to call me? The Pista!
And I'm Cecilia Immergreen, the ancient automaton.
Spin to win!
This is Raora Panthera, and we are... Justice!
Just this, just like that. Just... get get go!
We're finally here! We're so excited to witness Hololive English history with all of you. Are you ready to join a new chapter in Hololive English history?
The concert starts now! Get ready, and remember to enjoy it until the very last moment. Yippee! Here we go, is everyone ready?
Three, two, one!
Breaking Dimensions!
Look up at the horizon together as one
A star is on the rise and it's only begun
The pivotal moment we're clamoring for
An infinite future's at our door
Yeah
It's a timeless story with a new feel
Not just allegory, it's real
Wake up, big dreams about to come true
That means it's time to break through
Never knew we could make it so far,
But we're striving, thriving, here we are
Achieving the impossible
We're virtually unstoppable
We can't sit still, we just keep moving
Now everybody sing!
We're making our way to the next dimension,
We'll reinvent the world that we live in
We'll greet every day with new intentions
Break conventions, run right through!
This is it!
Been smashing barriers left and right
That's our myth!
Strong as we ever were, scaling heights
It's endless!
So get together, let's reunite!
Reach up, reach out, the future's bright.
We've been together for what feels like an eternity,
The times are changing, but we're ready for infinity, yeah
Our stories align, we're gonna go far when we combine
So look at the horizon and then look beyond,
We'll marvel at the skies and the strength of our bond,
We're making a vow to the smiling stars,
A powerful moment that's all ours
The seasons change, but we keep shining
Now everybody sing!
Keep it going!
We're making our way to the next dimension,
A million thrills in every direction
We'll give every mile our full attention,
Breaking tension, breaking through
We won't miss!
With endless energy, stronger ties
We got this!
A perfect harmony we devise
We promise!
So clap along with me
Time to rise!
The future's right before our eyes.
A new dimension of freedom that we've found,
We're breaking out of the mold, no longer bound
We're gonna spring to life and break the chains
Turn up the hype, can't be contained
We're shaking up the status quo,
No time to stop, we're good to go!
The whole wide world is listening,
So everybody sing!
We're making our way to the next dimension,
We're living out the dreams we believe in,
Excitement beyond our comprehension,
There's no question, we'll break through!
Don't relent!
We'll keep aspiring to excel
It's advent!
It's awe-inspiring, going well
Represent!
So light the fire and let's rebel!
The future's brighter, we can tell!
In every universe, we were always meant to meet
A little boundless search, we will never know defeat
My wings will guide your hands as the faithful days go by
We will count a pepper for a never-ending sky
Drawing on stalk together, I can sense another...
Where she's coming true, each time, every weather strengthens our crew.
ooh~
Just look around and see, it's so incredible!
So many smiles in a sea of light
Take one step with me and you'll be dazzled,
There's magic in the air tonight
The hours zoom zoom zoom
My heart goes boom boom boom
The world is brighter because you believe in me
Let's shout it loud loud loud
Our time is right now
We're on the edge of destiny
For a moment, I can dream with you
Every miracle we hoped for might come true
We come together, reaching out from far and wide,
And suddenly, you're here by my side!
When our voices and hearts unite, we're gonna shine bright!
Together, we're all for one.
(Let's sing! All for one!)
The thrill of happiness is all around us!
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
(Let's sing! All for one!!)
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
Hey!
All that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward,
We're singing, all for one!
All for one!
Let's go!
One, two, three, let's go!
Lost hope in love, I thought I'd never understand
Couldn't help it when you took my hand
Roads I ignored before, you left me wanting more
Destroyed everything just to get a bit ahead
Neon lights fly by, is it fake or reality?
Not sure of much, but know I'm ready
Soaring these streets, make me complete
Full throttle, come give me your all
Engine's not keeping up
With the beat of my heart, just can't get enough
Revving up, make it fast
Only us, make it last
Till the sun's up (one, two, three, let's go!)
'Nother shot in the dark, take me away
Fizzing up in my heart, it's all okay
Accelerate me until I'm there
You and I reach the line, mark the end
But we'll (let's go!) keep on goin' until the bubbles fade
I don't care if I don't see another day
Shocking in my heart, give me all that you got
Windows down, don't hesitate a minute more
Time is up, not enough, fill it up and don't look back again
Carbonated love
One, two, three, let's go!
Took a bet on love, it's better than I coulda dreamed
Look at what we've done, we're too extreme
Pour me your favorite drink, so much until we sink
Down to the bottom, don't wanna miss a thing
The track we're on might crash, oh what am I to do?
Rushing in, ignoring old avenues
Race through the night, my guiding light
Sparkling, I'm right here with you
Engine's not keeping up
With the beat of my heart, just can't get enough
Revving up, make it fast
Only us, make it last
Till the sun's up (one, two, three, let's go!)
'Nother shot in the dark, take me away
Fizzing up in my heart, it's all okay
Accelerate me until I'm there
You and I reach the line, mark the end
But we'll (let's go!) keep on goin' until the bubbles fade
I don't care if I don't see another day
Shocking in my heart, give me all that you got
Windows down, don't hesitate a minute more
Time is up, not enough, fill it up and don't look back again
Carbonated love
Come overflow my cup, I'm empty without you
Make such a mess of me, don't care if I'm the fool
Another night of bliss, speed up, let's make it new
Love me despite the way I'm crazy just for you
'Nother shot in the dark, take me away
Fizzing up in my heart, it's all okay
Accelerate me until I'm there
You and I reach the line, mark the end
But we'll (let's go!) keep on going until the bubbles fade
I don't care if I don't see another day
Shocking in my heart, give me all that you got
Windows down, don't hesitate a minute more
Love the rush, we shouldn't, don't give up, fire it up again
Our time is up, not enough, fill it up and begin
Carbonated love
just like the seasons change, you came so suddenly
"my feelings can't be swayed", you said that to me
you spun a web, your eyes hid truth inside a lie
you can't love me,
can't set me free
you made me love you more than i was ready for
was it that easy to make me all yours?
and as the seasons changed, you left me with this pain
nothing to lose, so i'll find you
my mind is filled up by you, it's my fault for trusting in a facade that you sold
My mind is filled up by you, trusting a facade you sold.
i'm wandering every street desperate for you to see
Thank you, New York!
ふわふわ モコモコ
Fuwa Fuwa, Moco Moco
魔界乃番犬シスターズ☆★
Demon realm guard dog sisters☆★
この世界に爆誕“BAU”DOL です
Born in this world, we're "BAU"DOLs!
BAUBAU!!
BAU BAU!!
フワワ
Fuwawa!!
モココ
Mococo!!
fuwa+moco は fuwamoco (fuwamoco!!)
Fuwa+moco is fuwamoco (fuwamoco!!)
フワワ
Fuwawa!!
モココ
Mococo!!
fuwa+moco は fuwamoco (fuwamoco!!)
Fuwa+moco is fuwamoco (fuwamoco!!)
フワワ
Fuwawa!!
モココ
Mococo!!
fuwa+moco は fuwamoco (fuwamoco!!)
Fuwa+moco is fuwamoco (fuwamoco!!)
BAUBAU~!!
BAU BAU~!
wake up したら 君 に morning
When I wake up, morning comes to you,
new な 出会い 鼻 利か せ search し て
Searching for new encounters with a keen nose.
ドキ ドキ doggy 右 に 左
Thumping, beating doggy, right and left.
bau bau bau
悩ん でい て も 来 ちゃう future
Even when worrying, the future comes anyway.
まずは 目 の 前 の 道 step し て
First, step onto the path right before us!
happy lucky puppy
一緒に 歩こ う よ
let's walk together!
ドーナツ の 穴 の 中 に は
Inside the donut's hole, surely...
きっと きっと 夢 が 詰まってる から
surely dreams are packed inside!
ふわふわ （wa!! foo!!）
Fuwa fuwa (Wa!! Foo!!)
もこもこ （come on!!）
Moco moco (Come on!!)
魔界乃番犬シスターズ☆★
Demon realm guard dog sisters☆★
2 匹 が 揃え ば もう 大騒ぎ
When the two of us get together, it's a ruckus!
もあ もあ （motto!!）
More more (Motto!!)
ハロハロ （BAUBAU!!）
Hello hello (BAU BAU!!)
迷わず に go my way
Without hesitation, go my way!
君 の 絶対 味方 “BAU”DOL です
We're your absolute ally, "BAU"DOLs!
フワワ
Fuwawa!!
モココ
Mococo!!
fuwa+moco は fuwamoco (fuwamoco!!)
Fuwa+moco is fuwamoco (fuwamoco!!)
フワワ
Fuwawa!!
モココ
Mococo!!
fuwa+moco は fuwamoco (fuwamoco!!)
Fuwa+moco is fuwamoco (fuwamoco!!)
BAUBAU~!!
BAU BAU~!
ひとり じゃ ない よ we’re together
We're not alone, we're together.
heart 繋がっ てる 君 と chat し て
Connected hearts, chatting with you.
fluffy fuzzy yappy
一緒に 歌お う よ
let's sing together!
ドーナツ の 穴 の 向こう へ
Beyond the donut's hole, surely...
きっと きっと 君 が 待っ て いる から
surely you're waiting for us!
ふわふわ （wa!! foo!!）
Fuwa fuwa (Wa!! Foo!!)
もこもこ （come on!!）
Moco moco (Come on!!)
魔界乃番犬シスターズ☆★
Demon realm guard dog sisters☆★
2 匹 が 揃え ば もう 止まら ない
When the two of us get together, there's no stopping us!
お 耳 も （ear!!）
Ears too (Ear!!)
尻尾 も （bunbun!!）
Tail too (Bunbun!!)
お 触り は 厳禁××
No touching allowedxx!
スリル 満点 爆弾 “BAU”DOL です
Thrill-packed explosive "BAU"DOLs!
BAUBAU!!
BAU BAU!!
「Hey!! Ruffians!! Kept you waiting, huh? Can I get a heck yeah!? Let’s shout “BAU”!!」
Hey!! Ruffians!! Kept you waiting, huh? Can I get a heck yeah!? Let’s shout “BAU”!!
BAU!! BAU!! BAU!! BAU!!
「Now, hear the howling of my soul!! Are you ready!?」
Now, hear the howling of my soul!! Are you ready!?
「Mococo-chan!! この 曲 は 可愛く 歌お う ねっ て 言った でしょ!!」
Mococo-chan!! You said we'd sing this song cute!!
「bau bau」
Bau bau...
「じゃあ b メロ から… せーの！」
Alright, from the B melody... Ready, go!
ドーナツ リング に 誓っ て
Swearing on the donut ring,
ずっと ずっと 笑顔 を 守る から
forever and ever, we'll protect your smiles!
ふわふわ （wa!! foo!!）
Fuwa fuwa (Wa!! Foo!!)
もこもこ （come on!!）
Moco moco (Come on!!)
魔界乃番犬シスターズ☆★
Demon realm guard dog sisters☆★
2 匹 が 揃え ば もう 大騒ぎ
When the two of us get together, it's a ruckus!
もあ もあ （motto!!）
More more (Motto!!)
ハロハロ （BAUBAU!!）
Hello hello (BAU BAU!!)
迷わず に go my way
Without hesitation, go my way!
君 の 絶対 味方 “BAU”DOL です
We're your absolute ally, "BAU"DOLs!
Hey, Ruffians!
Calculating high!
Can I get a heck yeah?
Let's shout bau!
Bau! Bau! Bau! Bau! Bau! Bau!
Bau! Bau!
Now, hear the howling of my soul!
Are you ready!? Bau! Bau!
Mococo-chan!
Bau! Bau!
モコちゃん！この曲は可愛く歌おうねって言ったでしょ！
Mococo-chan! You said we'd sing this song cute!
わうぼい
Wah-boy!
じゃあBメロから…せーの！
Alright, from the B melody... Ready, go!
どんな スリング に 誓っ て
Swearing in our slings,
ずっと ずっと 笑顔 を 守る から
forever and ever, we'll protect your smiles!
ふわふわ （wa!! foo!!）
Fuwa fuwa (Wa!! Foo!!)
もこもこ （come on!!）
Moco moco (Come on!!)
魔界乃番犬シスターズ☆★
Demon realm guard dog sisters☆★
2 匹 が 揃え ば もう 大騒ぎ
When the two of us get together, it's a ruckus!
もあ もあ （motto!!）
More more (Motto!!)
ハロハロ （BAUBAU!!）
Hello hello (BAU BAU!!)
迷わず に go my way
Without hesitation, go my way!
君 の 絶対 味方 “BAU”DOL です
We're your absolute ally, "BAU"DOLs!
フワワ
Fuwawa!!
モココ
Mococo!!
fuwa+moco は fuwamoco (fuwamoco!!)
Fuwa+moco is fuwamoco (fuwamoco!!)
フワワ
Fuwawa!!
モココ
Mococo!!
fuwa+moco は fuwamoco (fuwamoco!!)
Fuwa+moco is fuwamoco (fuwamoco!!)
BAUBAU~!!
BAU BAU~!
この 世界 に 爆誕 “BAU”DOL です
Born in this world, we're "BAU"DOLs!
BAUBAU!!
BAU BAU!!
フワワ
Fuwawa!!
モココ
Mococo!!
fuwa+moco は fuwamoco (fuwamoco!!)
Fuwa+moco is fuwamoco (fuwamoco!!)
フワワ
Fuwawa!!
モココ
Mococo!!
fuwa+moco は fuwamoco (fuwamoco!!)
Fuwa+moco is fuwamoco (fuwamoco!!)
BAUBAU~!!
BAU BAU~!
ふわふわ （wa!! foo!!）
Fuwa fuwa (Wa!! Foo!!)
もこもこ （come on!!）
Moco moco (Come on!!)
魔界乃番犬シスターズ☆★
Demon realm guard dog sisters☆★
2 匹 が 揃え ば もう 大騒ぎ
When the two of us get together, it's a ruckus!
もあ もあ （motto!!）
More more (Motto!!)
ハロハロ （BAUBAU!!）
Hello hello (BAU BAU!!)
fuwamoco is fuwamoco!
BAUBAU~!
BAU BAU~!
Welcome everyone to hololive English 2nd concert,
Breaking
Dimensions!
Bau Bau!
Thank you for all your Bau Bau lights! Thank you!
Oh, those Bau Bau lights! Thank you! Thank you so much!
Thank you so much!
You know, we were a bit worried that you wouldn't know who we are, 'cause you know, we're still new.
Yeah, but I don't think we have to worry, right Mococo?
No, thank you!
Thank you!
But first, Fuwawa, let's introduce ourselves.
Okay.
I'm... Fuwawa Abyssgard! I'm... Fuwawa Abyssgard!
Bau Bau, thank you! And we know it.
I'm... Mococo Abyssgard! I'm... Mococo Abyssgard!
You know, we're the real hololive English Advent's twin demon guard dogs!
We are... Fuwawa Abyssgard!
Bau Bau!
Thank you! Thank you for all your blue and pink lights!
Bau Bau! Thank you!
You know, that song that we just performed...
is our original song, meant to be "Bau Bau"! Thank you so much, did you have fun?
Yeah! With us!
Oh, did you hear that? Mococo, did you hear that?
Yeah, I heard it! Thank you!
Thank you!
Well, today, a big dream of ours came true.
Yeah, and that was being here together with you!
To perform our first original concert, with you,
you know, I... if it's okay,
I'd like to be a bit selfish. Selfish?
Yeah, is that okay? I have another dream.
Can we grant it all together? If that's okay,
Mococo, what kind of dream? Well,
I would like to hear you Bau Bau your biggest Bau Bau you ever Bau Bau'd!
Can you do that for us?
Okay, okay. Mococo, let's open here first. Over here? Okay. Everybody over here, on three...
Three, two, one,
Three, two, one, Bau Bau!
Thank you! Okay, then over here.
Okay, everybody over here now. Once more.
Three, two, one, Bau Bau!
Okay. Bau Bau.
Now, everybody all together, okay?
Here we go. Three, two, one, Bau Bau!
Bau Bau! Thank you so much, everybody!
Was that another dream came true?
Yeah! Bau Bau! You know, today
is all about breaking dimensions, yeah. And to us,
breaking dimensions, it's all about breaking it to you.
Yeah, breaking it to you! Yeah, that's literally it! You know,
we want to be able to break it to your heart, you know, it's like, "Hello!" "Hello!"
I really like to break it! Yeah! Yeah! I'm breaking it to your heart!
Yeah, we're going to break it, we're going to protect that smile!
And you know, breaking the dimensions, it also means being here all together and getting pumped up to make a night you'll never forget.
Are you ready? Yeah!
Bau Bau!
You know, it's a... it's a very exciting night, but there's... there's been a misunderstanding.
There's been a misunderstanding! I thought it's breaking the dimensions, but everybody is joining us on YouTube today.
Well, the end of this sneak peek is right here! And you can join us over at spawn!
Or CV Plus. So please get your paws on this!
Okay? Okay, get your CV! Thank you, please! Thank you! Bau Bau!
have one more thing I wanted to
Look what's here, more!
Yeah!
I've been so selfish!
Is that okay?
So... when...
You know, like the yellow...
All together! Yeah!
The title of today's concert, okay?
Are we ready?
We're gonna do that lots today, okay?
Uh-huh! Okay!
Here we all go, then.
Breaking...
Dimensions!
Are we ready?
We're gonna do that lots today, okay?
Okay!
Here we all go, then.
Breaking...
look up at the horizon together as one
a star is on the rise and it's only begun
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.